Thomas Chester "Chet" Edwards State Legislative papers, Inclusive: 1957-1991, Bulk: 1982-1990.
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
Thomas Chester "Chet" Edwards State Legislative papers
Inclusive: 1957-1991, Bulk: 1982-1990.
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials http://www.baylor.edu/lib/bcpm/
8
Edwards, Chet
224 document boxes
The Thomas Chester "Chet" Edwards State Legislative papers consist of personal and political materials from Mr. Edwards's 8-year career in the Texas Senate. Records include legislation, correspondence, topical files, and other materials.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
Chet Edwards was born in Corpus Christi, Nueces County, Texas, November 24, 1951. In 1974, he graduated Magna Cum Laude with a B.A. in Economics from Texas A&M University. Edwards worked for three years from 1974-1977 for Congressman Olin E. "Tiger" Teague as a legislative and district administrative assistant in the 6th district of Texas. Congressman Teague was the most highly decorated World War II veteran in Congress and was known for 32 years as "Mr. Veteran" in Congress. At the age of 26, Edwards was encouraged by Congressman Teague to become his successor in 1978. Congressman Edwards narrowly lost in the Democratic primary to Phil Gramm, but went on to earn an MBA from the Harvard Business School in 1981. In the 1980's, Edwards worked as a marketing representative at the Trammell Crow Company in commercial real estate. Additionally, he owned and was the president of Edwards Communications, a rural radio station in South Texas.
Edwards began his 28-year public service career as a state senator, being elected in 1982 as the youngest member of the Texas Senate at age 30. From 1983 to 1990, Edwards served Central Texas District 9 in the Texas Senate, participating in the 68th-71st Legislatures. He was on the Health and Human Resources Committee, and chaired the Senate Nominations Committee. Edwards was also chairman of the Texas Sunset Commission, a joint commission which reviews state agencies on a 12-year rotation, as well as chair of the Texas Election Code Revision Committee, and the Committee on Business, Technology, and Education.
Edwards had a number of legislative accomplishments during his time in the Texas Senate. As a member of Senate committees on education, he was a champion for making educational improvements, including public education reform and education for women and minorities in engineering. He was also a champion of High Technology economic development legislation which included research on the Superconducting Super Collider. His labor legislation reformed workers’ compensation, and business legislation dealt with trucking deregulation, and the Texas Growth Fund. Edwards was also involved in Health and Human Services by strengthening the Board of Medical Examiners, chairing the Sunset Commission and passing Texas Department of Human Services legislation, and requiring criminal background checks for nursing home employees. He was also known as a champion for Texas’s senior citizens, was influential in agriculture, worked on consumer legislation, including compromise on AT&T deregulation, and reformed the primary election process by passing Super Tuesday legislation.
Edwards received the “Texas Business” Award during the 68th Regular Session as one of three outstanding freshman legislators. He was named one of the Ten Best Legislators by Texas Monthly magazine in 1985.
Edwards was elected as a congressman in 1990, serving in the U.S. House of Representatives from 1991-2010. He served as a member on the House Budget Committee, the Appropriations Committee, and the Financial Services Appropriations Subcommittee, and as vice chair of the Energy and Water Appropriations Subcommittee. He also co-chaired the House Army Caucus.
Congressman Edwards was known as a national champion for America's veterans, troops, and their families. After becoming Chairman of the Military Construction and Veterans Affairs Appropriations Subcommittee in 2007, Congressman Edwards authored a huge increase in funding for veterans health care and benefits, the largest increase in veterans funding in the history of the Veterans Administration. Edwards also played a key role in enacting the 21st Century GI Bill of Rights into law, covering the full cost of a college education for our troops. When he represented Fort Hood, the world's largest Army base, Congressman Edwards played a major leadership role in support of the U.S. Army, troops, and military families. He was co-chair of the House Army Caucus for over a decade and served on the House Armed Services and Veterans Affairs Committees for six years before joining the Appropriations Committee.
Edwards became known as a leader in the fight against nuclear terrorism, and in 2001, strongly opposed cuts to the nuclear non-proliferation budget proposed by the Bush Administration. Serving as a member on the Energy and Water Appropriations Subcommittee, Edwards helped to oversee key homeland defense and university research programs to protect Americans from the threat of nuclear terrorism.
During his 20-year tenure in Congress, including 12 years of seniority on the powerful Appropriations Committee, Congressman Edwards developed a reputation of working hard and effectively for his Central Texas constituents. This reputation was the result of his commitment to protecting jobs and the local economy by making vital federal investments in key education, health, transportation, and water programs in his District.
Edwards is known as a fiscal conservative who believes massive federal deficits and the multi-trillion national debt are harmful to our economy and morally wrong to pass on to our children and grandchildren. He adopted a pro-economic, pro-agriculture record which earned him several endorsements, and was known as a supporter of Second Amendment rights.
As a respected voice on issues facing working families, Edwards pushed for increased access to health care for children of working families under the State Children's Health Insurance Program (S-CHIP), supported middle class tax cuts, and protected Medicare and Social Security benefits for America's seniors. Edwards was also recognized as a defender of religious liberty.
Since leaving Congress in 2011, Edwards was appointed the W. R. Poage Distinguished Chair of Public Service at Baylor University. He established Edwards, Davis Stover & Associates, LLC with his former chief of staff, Lindsey Davis Stover, and continues to be involved with veterans issues in the Washington, D.C. area through his work on the boards of the Military Child Education Coalition and the Arlington National Cemetery Advisory Commission.
Scope and Content
The Chet Edwards State Legislative papers cover an expanse of 1957-1991, although the majority of the records span 1982-1990, from the 67th through the 71st Legislatures. Collection materials are based on Edwards’ service as a Texas State Senator from 1983-1990, and materials are comprised of House and Senate Bills and Resolutions, correspondence, topical files, and other administrative materials. Each session of Congress has been organized into a series, and these particular materials are repeated within each series. These materials discuss a wide variety of important issues from the 1980’s in Central Texas, including Abortion, Blue Laws, Budget Crisis and Taxation, Criminal Justice, DWI and Drinking Age, Education, Elderly Care, Elections, Health and Healthcare, High Technology economics, Pari-Mutuel Gambling, Trucking Deregulation, Utilities, and Workers’ Compensation.
Arrangement
Prior to this finding aid, the Chet Edwards State papers were unorganized, though folders of like materials were often grouped together, and an inventory existed. During processing, a series arrangement was imposed. Many existing folders within the new Topical, House and Senate Bills and Resolutions, and Administrative subseries were simply retitled and then ordered alphabetically, while the Correspondence subseries was reworked. Correspondence within each series was previously unorganized, or organized in alphabetical order by constituent last name. This was rearranged to more helpfully reflect topics of correspondence. These topics were then ordered alphabetically.
The final arrangement has six series: I. Administrative, II. 67th Session, III. 68th Session, IV. 69th Session, V. 70th Session, and VI. 71st Session. Series III-VI also contain subseries: Correspondence, Senate Bills, Senate Resolutions, House Bills, House Resolutions, Topical, and Administrative.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to the W. R. Poage Legislative Library in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 8. Acquired 1990-12-20
Related Resources
Items in related collections
Thomas Chester "Chet" Edwards U.S. House of Representatives papers, Inclusive: 1990-2010, Bulk: 1991-2010
Related references
“Edwards, Thomas Chester (Chet).” Biographical Directory of the United States Congress. Accessed June 18, 2015.
Edwards, Chet. "Chet Edwards: He's Working for Us." 2016.
Thomas Chester "Chet" Edwards State Legislative Papers, Accession #8, Baylor Collections of Political Materials, W. R. Poage Legislative Library, Baylor University.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Edwards, Chet, 1951- -- Archives.
Subjects (Organizations)
Texas. Legislature. Senate.
Places
Texas -- Politics and government.
Subjects
Educational law and legislation -- Texas.; Election law -- Texas.; High technology industries -- Texas.; Legislators -- Texas -- Archives.; Legislators -- United States -- Archives.; Medicaid -- Texas.; Medical care -- Law and legislation -- Texas.; Workers' compensation -- Texas.
Genres
Correspondence.; Legislative materials.; Records (Documents)
- Administrative, 1974-1990; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  This series covers Edwards’ entire Texas Senate career and includes materials related to administrative tasks, such as campaign and travel expenses, guest registers, and system and formatting instructions. This series also includes Legislative accomplishments and reports, county-specific constituent requests, and biographical materials. Of particular note is a folder of collected and copied materials related to “Tiger” Teague, Edwards’s mentor.
  - Biographical, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Biographical, Olin “Tiger” Teague, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Campaign Expenses, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Chet Edwards for Congress, 1979-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Requests, Dallas County, 1982-1983 August (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Constituent Requests, Dallas County, 1983 August-December (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Constituent Requests, Dallas County, 1983 December-1984 August (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Constituent Requests, Dallas County, 1986, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Constituent Requests, Ellis County, 1983 January-November (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Constituent Requests, Ellis County, 1983 November-1984 February (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Constituent Requests, Ellis County, 1984 February-June (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Constituent Requests, Ellis County, 1984 June-November (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Constituent Requests, Ellis County, 1985-1987, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Constituent Requests, Falls County, 1982 March-1985 March (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Constituent Requests, Freestone County, 1982 November-1983 October (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Constituent Requests, Freestone County, 1983 November-1984 July (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Requests, Freestone County, 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Constituent Requests, Henderson County, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Henderson County, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Requests, Henderson County, Athens Nursing Home, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Constituent Requests, Hill County, 1983 January-1984 June (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Constituent Requests, Hill County, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Constituent Requests, Limestone County, 1982 November-1985 March (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Constituent Requests, Limestone County, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Constituent Requests, McLennan County, 1982 June-August (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Constituent Requests, McLennan County, 1983 September-1984 January (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Constituent Requests, McLennan County, 1984 February-November (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Requests, McLennan County, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Constituent Requests, McLennan County, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Constituent Requests, Navarro County, 1983 February-1985 January (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Constituent Requests, Navarro County, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Constituent Requests, Out-of-District, 1982 August-1983 January (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Constituent Requests, Out-of-District, 1983 February-October (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Constituent Requests, Out-of-District, 1983 November-1985 February, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Constituent Requests, Out-of-District, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Guest Register, 1983 January-1986 April (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Guest Register, 1986 May-1987 May (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Guest Register, 1987 May-1990 February (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Guest Register, Duncanville Campaign Office Opening, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Reports and Chet Edwards’ Accomplishments, 69th-71st sessions, 1986-1989 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Memorandums, Mail and Supply Requests, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Nominations Subcommittee, Appointments, 1979 May-1979 August (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Nominations Subcommittee, Appointments, 1979 May-1980 September (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Nominations Subcommittee, Correspondence Information System (CIS) Instructions, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Nominations Subcommittee, Formats Instructions, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Nominations Subcommittee, Legislative Applications System Instructions, 1984, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Open Records Act, Request for Senator Edwards’ Budget, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Travel Expense Reports, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- 67th Session, 1981-1983; 2
  This series includes topical materials from the 67th Legislature, 1981-1982. It is important to note that Edwards was not yet a Senator during this session.
  - Budget Estimates, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Chamber of Commerce and District Court: Hill County, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Press Releases, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Republicans/Bad Issue File, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Texas Youth Council, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Texas Youth Council (1 of 2), 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Texas Youth Council (2 of 2), 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Utilities, Lignite Supply Agreement, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- 68th Session, 1973-1988; 3
  This series contains papers from the 68th Legislature, 1983-1984. This was Edwards’s first session in the Texas Senate. It contains subseries: Correspondence, Senate Bills, Senate Resolutions, House Bills, Topical, and Administrative. A few topics of importance among these subseries are budget crisis, education, health, Blue Law, DWI and drinking age, election code, oil and gasoline, the Public Utilities Commission, pari-mutuel gambling, redistricting, and trucking deregulation. The Administrative subseries refers to materials related to administrative tasks, session wrap-up, appointments, columns and press releases, or various materials that relate to the legislative session as a whole.
  - Correspondence, 1982-1985; 1
    - Abortion, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Ad Valorem Taxes, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Advertising Tax, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Agency Funds Management, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture (1 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture (2 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Animal Treatment, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Automobiles, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Banking, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Blue Law (1 of 4), 1983 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Blue Law (2 of 4), 1983 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Blue Law (3 of 4), 1983 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Blue Law (4 of 4), 1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Brewing, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Brucellosis, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Cattle, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Child Care, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Child and Elderly Protective Services, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Child Safety Seats, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Child Support, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Coastal and Marine, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Common Carriers Regulation (1 of 4), 1983 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Common Carriers Regulation (2 of 4), 1983 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Common Carriers Regulation (3 of 4), 1983 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Common Carriers Regulation (4 of 4), 1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Community Affairs Block Grants, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Comptroller Bullock’s Corsicana Office Closing, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Constituent Requests (1 of 5), 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Constituent Requests (2 of 5), 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Constituent Requests (3 of 5), 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Constituent Requests (4 of 5), 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Constituent Requests (5 of 5), 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Credit Cards, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Criminal Justice (1 of 4), 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Criminal Justice (2 of 4), 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Criminal Justice (3 of 4), 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Criminal Justice (4 of 4), 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Dentistry (1 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Dentistry (2 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Disabled Employment, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - District Clerk Fees, 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Drug Abuse, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - DWI and Drinking Age (1 of 6), 1983 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - DWI and Drinking Age (2 of 6), 1983 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - DWI and Drinking Age (3 of 6), 1983 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - DWI and Drinking Age (4 of 6), 1983 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - DWI and Drinking Age (5 of 6), 1983 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - DWI and Drinking Age (6 of 6), 1983 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Ear Mold Bill, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Economics, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Education, Community Colleges, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Education, Elected Board of Education, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Education, General (1 of 10), 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Education, General (2 of 10), 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Education, General (3 of 10), 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Education, General (4 of 10), 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Education, General (5 of 10), 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Education, General (6 of 10), 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Education, General (7 of 10), 1982-1984 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Education, General (8 of 10), 1982-1984 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Education, General (9 of 10), 1982-1984 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Education, General (10 of 10), 1982-1984 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Education, Higher Education (1 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Education, Higher Education (2 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Education, Homeschooling, 1982-1984 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Education, Permanent University Fund, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Education, Public Education Reform (1 of 13), 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Education, Public Education Reform (2 of 13), 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Education, Public Education Reform (3 of 13), 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Education, Public Education Reform (4 of 13), 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Education, Public Education Reform (5 of 13), 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Education, Public Education Reform (6 of 13), 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Education, Public Education Reform (7 of 13), 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Education, Public Education Reform (8 of 13), 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Education, Public Education Reform (9 of 13), 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Education, Public Education Reform (10 of 13), 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Education, Public Education Reform (11 of 13), 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Education, Public Education Reform (12 of 13), 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Education, Public Education Reform (13 of 13), 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Education, Public School Finance (1 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Education, Public School Finance (2 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Education, Public School Finance (3 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Education, Teacher Pay Raises (1 of 4), 1982-1984 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Education, Teacher Pay Raises (2 of 4), 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Education, Teacher Pay Raises (3 of 4), 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Education, Teacher Pay Raises (4 of 4), 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Education, Teacher Retirement System (1 of 5), 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Education, Teacher Retirement System (2 of 5), 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Education, Teacher Retirement System (3 of 5), 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Education, Teacher Retirement System (4 of 5), 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Education, Teacher Retirement System (5 of 5), 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Education, University Interscholastic League (1 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Education, University Interscholastic League (2 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Education, Vocational Education (1 of 2), 1984 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Education, Vocational Education (2 of 2), 1984 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Elderly and Aging (1 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Elderly and Aging (2 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Equal Employment, 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Emergency Management, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Engineering, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Environment (1 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Environment (2 of 2), 1982-1984 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Ethics Commission, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Election Code Revision, 1982-1984 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Election Code Revision (1 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Election Code Revision (2 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Election Redistricting, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Election, General, 1982-1984 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Elevator and Rides Regulations, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Family Violence, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Farm Worker’s Compensation, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Firearms, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Fireworks, 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Forestry, Parks, and Wildlife (1 of 3), 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Forestry, Parks, and Wildlife (2 of 3), 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Forestry, Parks, and Wildlife (3 of 3), 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Free Trade Zones, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - General (1 of 22), 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - General (2 of 22), 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - General (3 of 22), 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - General (4 of 22), 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - General (5 of 22), 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 1)